Hello everyone and hello fellow sunlifers.
Before we begin let me introduce myself.
I am like a Placido unit manager of
Tiger Treasure.
And for today's video, I would love to
share with you the most affordable plan
of Sunl and that is Sunl Assure.  Okay
, let's start.
Make a bright choice with Sunlife
Assure, a critical illness insurance
product that primarily helps address
your needs for health protection.
So, what's inside the Sunlife Assure?
What is wrong with him?   Let's
take it one by one.  First, we have
critical illness coverage or benefit.
Its coverage is 36 major
critical illnesses.  And of course, life
insurance protection.  And this plan
is 5 years to pay and only insured
until 5 years.  And it is renewable.
Just wait, I'll delete it.
My letter was too long.  Wait.
There you go.
renewable every 5 years and insured
for 5 years as well.
And this plan is this provides
protection until age 70 regardless of
your health condition.
This plan is called term insurance.  That's why
it's called term insurance,
you only pay for a short time period which is 5
years.
That's only 5 years old and he's only been insured for 5 years
.  That's the term
insurance.  That's why Sunlife assure is
Sunlife's most affordable plan.  So
what's inside?
I'll just make it bigger.
We have a primary benefit with a face
amount of 500,000.  This is the lowest
here at Asure.  When
we say face amount, this is
our benefit in planning.  This is not
the total amount you would pay if
this were not the benefit.  So no matter how much
the face amount is, that's automatically
our coverage.
500,000 also, either critical illness
or life insurance, whichever comes
first.
And we have additional benefits here.
Aside from the primary benefit, we
have additional benefits or riders.  There,
we have an accidental death benefit of
Php500,000.
If the face amount is
automatic, that is the accidental death
benefit.  So when we say accidental death
benefit upon death of the insured is due to
accident, Sunlife will pay an additional
500,000 to the beneficiaries plus
the 500k coverage will be 1m
.  And we have total disability
benefits, so if the insured is
totally disabled and has not yet
finished paying for 5 years and that happens
, Sunlife will wave the payment.
Sunl continue the payment until 5 years.
Okay.
So for a male 34 years old non-soccer,
actually, don't be surprised
by this plan. Is this for the rich?
You couldn't afford it when he was rich
because look at it
quarterly, it's php11.13,
is php13 cheap?  Very affordable.
Now if you make an annual payment of
Ph495.
Because you watched my video, I'll
give you a 10% discount.   It's
not true that Sunlife is giving a
10% discount on
our traditional plans.
It's automatic when you make an annual payment, there's a 10%
discount.  This is the 10%
discount.  Well,
if it's semi-annual, we have
semi-annual too.  5% discount, please.
So if you said it was for the rich,
you saw it, right?  It might be enough, but
your coverage is Php500,000.
That's why it's Sunlife's most affordable plan
.  Even though it's term insurance
, it's still
worth it.
His coverage is PH00,000.
And once your plan is approved
, starting from day one, you'll be insured
immediately.
Allr so let's go here to the critical
illness benefit.
Our critical illness benefit is
Php500,000.
The critical illness benefit is only activated
after 90 days of
plan approval.  So that means to say if for example
our plan is approved today, then
the 90-day count will start
.  Today is day one until 90 days.
Only then will
our critical illness benefit be activated.  And that's
only until age 70.
Is this plan
renewable up to A70?  So these are the
36 major critical illnesses.  Major major.
That's what usually
happens here.  So when
the insured develops a critical illness, they need to
be on the list to claim
the 500,000.  Okay?  What is he?  Either
health, either critical illness, it or
life.  Once you get this, of course
life is gone.
What's the first thing?
Okay.  There is also a chance that it will be
sunny.
We will not pay.  Sunl not going to pay
for any benefit.  What if you were
diagnosed with a critical illness in
less than 90 days?  So you need 91 and
above.
Okay.  And then there's also HIV
AIDS, a pre-existing medical condition.
If you have an existing
medical condition, please tell the
advisor what it is.  And
Sunlife will take care of it.  Sunlife will
decide whether
your plan will be approved or not.  Actually,
I have clients who have existing
medical conditions that are approved
.  Just don't be
super critical, that's what
won't be approved.  But don't be
afraid.  It's better for us to be
transparent with the advisor.
Okay.  And
the other, is this
renewable?  Right.
Answer.  Char might suddenly answer.
There you go.  So if you renew it after
5 years, this will be
your premium.  18328
quarterly.  That will be
your quarterly update for the next 5
years.  And so on.  5 years.  5 years.  5
years until age 70.
That's it.  Actually, this plan is good
.  To start.  If you really do
n't have a budget and want to be insured,
this plan is the best.  Because
his coverage is already big and he already has
health.  It depends on the budget.  If
this is really what our budget can handle
, why not?  'Right?  What's important is that
there is better protection than
nothing.  Just in case a critical
illness occurs.  Where do you get
a bag?
Is it PH00,000?  At least there is.
If you want to be sure, make
sure.  Or not?
Sunlife assure is the most affordable
plan of sunl with a life insurance or
critical illness benefit.
Think about your future.
Let's protect what matters most and that
is you.
Don't forget to like subscribe and share.
Thank you for watching.
[Music]